spreadex.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy | Terms & Agreements | Spreadex

**1\. DATA PRIVACY PROTECTION POLICY**  
Protecting the security and privacy of your personal information is important to Spreadex and to the way we conduct our business in compliance with laws on privacy, data protection and data security. We hope the policy outlined below will help you understand what information Spreadex may collect, how Spreadex uses and safeguards that information and with whom we may share it.

  **Spreadex Commitment to Data Privacy Protection**  
Through our websites, Spreadex will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g. your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address ("personal information")), unless you voluntarily choose to provide it to us (e.g. by registration, email enquiry, survey). If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it to us.   
When you do provide us with personal information, we usually use it to respond to your enquiry, or provide you access to specific account information, and to support our customer relationship with you.

We may disclose your personal information to our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.

We may disclose your personal information:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law (including, but not limited to, other regulatory bodies and/or law enforcement agencies);

(b) in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

(d) to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.

We may store and process personal information and share it within the Spreadex group of companies to better understand your business needs and how we can improve our products and services; or we (or a third party on our behalf) may use Personal Information to contact you about a Spreadex offer in support of your business needs or to conduct online surveys to understand better our customers' needs and profiles.  
If you choose not to have your personal information used to support our customer relationship programmes (especially direct-marketing or market-research), we will respect your choice. We do not now (and do not intend to in the future) sell, rent or otherwise market your personal information to third parties.  
When you open an account with Spreadex, depending on your stated trading preference on your application, you will be opted in to receive either a weekly financial market update email or regular sports emails highlighting key events or matches. We may also send you occasional emails on product improvements and special offers.    
You can opt out of receiving these emails at any time by clicking the 'unsubscribe' link at the top of Spreadex emails or by emailing [info@spreadex.com](mailto:info@spreadex.com) with your request.

**Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically**  
When you access our website, we may automatically (i.e. not by registration) collect information that is not personally identifiable (e.g. type of Internet browser and computer operating system used; domain name of the website from which you came; number of visits, average time spent, pages viewed). We may use this information and share it within the Spreadex Group of companies to measure the use of our website and improve its content.

**"Cookies" - Information Placed Automatically on Your Computer**  
When you view our website, we may store some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" to automatically recognise you the next time you visit. Cookies can help us in many ways, for example, by allowing us to tailor a website to better match your interests or to save your password so that you do not have to re-enter it each time. If you choose not to be recognised, please refer to your Internet browser to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.

**Children**  
No personal information should be submitted to Spreadex's websites by children without the consent of their parent or guardian. Spreadex encourages all parents or guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal information while using the Internet. Spreadex will not knowingly collect or use any personal information collected from children for any purpose whatsoever, including disclosure to third parties.

**Security**  
Spreadex takes precautions to ensure the security of your personal information and strives to keep it accurate. We carefully protect your personal information from loss, destruction, falsification, manipulation, and unauthorised access or unauthorised disclosure.

**Controlling interest based advertising and other third party cookies - showing advertising that is relevant to your interests on other sites.**  
Sometimes, to improve the effective of online advertising campaigns Spreadex may extend the number of times that you see same ad by purchasing advertising space on other sites that are deemed relevant by the advertiser. There are several ways to opt out of the process. This can be achieved by clicking on the following icon on the ad itself.  
  
In addition to the controls available on your computer there are also other ways of controlling interest based advertising and other tracking cookies and the links to each are provided below.  
• Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB) "Your Online Choices" page. This allows you to control interest based advertising from each of the ad networks represented by the IAB. [http://www.youronlinechoices.com ](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)  
• Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) control page. This allows you to control behavioural advertising from each of the ad networks represented by the NAI. <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>   
• Digital Advertising Alliance’s self-regulatory program for online behavioural advertising control page.   
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>[  
](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)**[  
](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)Casino  
** When you play casino slots developed by NetEnt, NetEnt’s privacy policy also applies. It can be found [here](https://www.netent.com/en/netent-privacy-policy-eu/).  ** _  
 _**

**Questions and Comments**  
If you have any questions or comments about Spreadex's Data Privacy Protection Policy please send an e-mail to [info@spreadex.com](mailto:info@spreadex.com) and insert the words "Data Privacy Protection Policy" in the "Subject" line. As the Internet matures, so will our Data Privacy Protection Policy. We will post changes to our Data Privacy Protection Policy on this page as soon as the commitment has been made to alter any existing policy.
